scriptreaderpro.com 2019-09-08

# Privacy Notice | Script Reader Pro

## **Privacy Notice**

This Privacy Notice explains how “Script Reader Pro” or “we” use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.

Script Reader Pro is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Script Reader Pro may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

By using our site, you consent to the following privacy notice.

#### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### **Controlling Your Personal Information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

#### **What Information Do We Collect About You?  **

We collect information about you when you fill in a contact form or email us directly. We also collect information when you voluntarily comment on our blog posts, provide feedback and sign up for our newsletter. Website usage information is collected using cookies (see below).

The information we collect about you may include; your name, email address, address, phone number, IP address, location, company name, sex, age, your chosen internet browser and service provider, and device plus any information you supply voluntarily.

#### **Cookies**

These are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

#### **How We Use Your Data**

We collect information about you to fulfill your request e.g. if you fill out a ‘contact us’ form we use this information to contact you directly, reply to your questions, process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about other products, services, and information we think may be of interest to you.

We may also contact you directly to follow up on the service and user experience we provide. We use your information collected from the website to personalize your repeat visits to our website.

If “Script Reader Pro” is ever sold to another company your contact information will be passed on to this new party. We will take cautionary measure to ensure we do not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee the above services to you.

#### **How Long Will We Store Your Data?  **

If Script Reader Pro provides any paid for services to you, we are required under tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information.

#### **Marketing**

We would like to send you updates and information about products and services of ours and other companies which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other parties. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes please click the unsubscribe button at the bottom of our newsletter or [contact us](https://www.scriptreaderpro.com/contact-us/) to let us know you no longer wish to be contacted.

#### **What Are Your Rights?  **

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us [here](https://www.scriptreaderpro.com/contact-us/). We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

#### **Links to Other Websites**

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies as once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.

Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### **Affiliates**

Sometimes we mention that a link is an affiliate link. This simply means sometimes we recommend a product or service and if you choose to purchase that product or service via my recommendation, we will get a small referral commission. Of course, this is at no extra cost to you but it does help keep our candle burning so we can keep bringing you great tips! We truly appreciate your support in this way. Thank you.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

## **Terms & Conditions**

If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Script Reader Pro’s relationship with you in relation to this website.

The term Script Reader Pro or “us” or “we” refers to the owner of the website. The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of our website.

♦ The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.

♦ Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.

♦ Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.

♦ This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.

♦ All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website. Unauthorized use of this website may give to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offense.

♦ This website may include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).

♦ Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the United States.

**The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only.**

The information is provided by Script Reader Pro and whilst we endeavor to keep the information up-to-date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of or in connection with the use of this website.

Through this website, you may be able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Script Reader Pro. We have no control over the nature, content, and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Script Reader Pro takes no responsibility for and will not be liable for the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

#### **Changes to Our Privacy Notice and Terms & Conditions**

We keep our privacy policy and terms and conditions under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This page was last updated on July 19, 2019.
